Faculty Reference; Collection ua950.003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Savitt, Joan, Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 39)
- Savitt, Joan Neuburger, Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 40)
- Saxx-Smith, Richard F., Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 41)
- Sayahi, Lotfi, Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 42)
- Sayginsoy, Ozgen, Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 43)
- Sayles, John M., Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 44)
- Scanlon, Donna, Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 45)
- Scatton, Ernest, 1976 (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 46)
- Schafer, Ronald R., Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 47)
- Schafer Ronald, Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 48)
- Schaefer, Vincent J., Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 49)
- Schaefer, Vincent, Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 50)
- Schaffer, Richard, Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 51)
- Schaninger, Charles M., Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 52)
- Schaninger, Charles M., Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 53)
- Scharl, Karl W., Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 54)
- Schatsky, Gary, Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 55)
- Schechter, Stephen L., Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 56)
- Scheck, Helene, Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 57)
- Schell, Lawrence, Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 58)
- Schell, Lawrence M., Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 59)
- Schermerhorn, Barbara, Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 60)
- Schieffelin, William, Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 61)
- Schimley, Mary L., Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 62)
- Schindler, Amy C., 2002 (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 63)
- Schlesinger, Arthur, Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 64)
- Schlesinger, George, Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 65)
- Schlesberg, Shirley, Undated (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 66)
- Schmidt, C. James, 1972 (Box 35 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 67)
- Schmidt, Dolores, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 1)
- Schmidt, Dolores B., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 2)
- Schmalberger, Donald C., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 3)
- Schmidt, J.T., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 4)
- Schmidt, John T., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 5)
- Schmidt, John T., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 6)
- Schmidt, Mark, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 7)
- Schmidt, Rudolph M., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 8)
- Schmidt, Rudolph M., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 9)
- Schmidt, Ruth A., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 10)
- Schmidt, Ruth Ann, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 11)
- Schobert, Timothy T., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 12)
- Scholes, Charles P., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 13)
- Scholes, Charles, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 14)
- Scholz, Wilfried W., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 15)
- Scholz, Wilfried, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 16)
- Schoolman, Morton, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 17)
- Schoonmaker, Barbara J., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 18)
- Schrader, Barbara H., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 19)
- Schrader, Edda, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 20)
- Schuerman, Donald W., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 21)
- Schuler Jr., Eugene K., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 22)
- Schulz, Joan, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 23)
- Schumacher, Jen, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 24)
- Schuyler, Eileen, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 25)
- Schwab, James J., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 26)
- Schwartz, Stanley, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 27)
- Schwartz, Stanley, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 28)
- Schworm, Ronald, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 29)
- Sci Mecca, Joseph, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 30)
- Scotland, Minnie Brink, 1918-1956 (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 31)
- Scott, Brian Y., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 32)
- Scott, Joel, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 33)
- Scott, Jon, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 34)
- Scott, Warren, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 35)
- Secor, Lynn J., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 36)
- Sedransk, Joseph, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 37)
- Sedransk, Nell, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 38)
- Sedransk, N. (also Cromie, W.J.), Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 39)
- Sedransk, N. (also Sedransk, J.), Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 40)
- Sedransk, N., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 41)
- Sedransk, Nell, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 42)
- Seeman, Nadrian C., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 43)
- Seidelman, Raymond, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 44)
- Selca, Frank, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 45)
- Sellen, Mary K., 1998 (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 46)
- Sellen, Mary, 2001 (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 47)
- Semprevivo, Phil, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 48)
- Semprevivo, Philip C., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 49)
- Serbalik, James, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 50)
- Serrone, David, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 51)
- Serven, Jesse R., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 52)
- Sewall, Murphy, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 53)
- Seymour, William, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 54)
- Shaffer, Kay L., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 55)
- Shahedipour-Sandvik, Fatemeh, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 56)
- Shanker, Albert, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 57)
- Shapiro, Stephen M., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 58)
- Shaw, Edward P., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 59)
- Shaw, William J., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 60)
- Shayne, Vivian T., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 61)
- Sheehan, Michael Terrence, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 62)
- Sheehan, William F., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 63)
- Sheehan, William F., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 64)
- Shenise, Robert W., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 65)
- Shepherd, David, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 66)
- Sherman, Edmund, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 67)
- Sherman, Lawrence W., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 68)
- Sherman, Lawrence, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 69)
- Sherman, Malcolm J., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 70)
- Sherman, Susan R., 1977 (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 71)
- Sherwin, Judith J., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 72)
- Sheu, Jim, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 73)
- Shields, Evelyn, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 74)
- Shirley, Robert C., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 75)
- Short, William, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 76)
- Short, William G., Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 77)
- Shub, Mina, Undated (Box 36 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 78)
- Shubb, David, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 1)
- Shuing Wu, Chun, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 2)
- Shumaker, John W., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 3)
- Shumaker, John, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 4)
- Shy, Oz, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 5)
- Siegel, Leslie, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 6)
- Silbiger, Sara, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 7)
- Silen, Juan Angel, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 8)
- Silva, Fred, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 9)
- Silverman, Bernard I., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 10)
- Silverman, Wendy K., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 11)
- Simches, Frances, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 12)
- Simmons, Gwendolyn, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 13)
- Simpson, Gordon, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 14)
- Simpson, Gordon J., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 15)
- Singal, C.M., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 16)
- Singh, Sadhu M., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 17)
- Sipay, Edward R., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 18)
- Sipe, H. Craig, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 19)
- Sipe, Craig, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 20)
- Sirotkin, Phillip L., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 21)
- Sisk, Henry L., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 22)
- Sivers, Cathryne H., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 23)
- Sivers, Cathryne H., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 24)
- Sivers, Elizabeth, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 25)
- Skeel, Richard H., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 26)
- Skeels, Harold M., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 27)
- Skemer, Don, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 28)
- Skemer, Don, 1987-1991 (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 29)
- Skemer, Don, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 30)
- Skidmore, Willard E., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 31)
- Skolnik, Sara, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 32)
- Slade, Leonard A. Jr., 1988 August 1 (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 33)
- Sloan, Anne T., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 34)
- Sloan, Anne, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 35)
- Slocum, John, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 36)
- Slyke, Henry, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 37)
- Small, Richard, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 38)
- Small, William D., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 39)
- Smiley, Malcolm F., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 40)
- Smirensky, Helen, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 41)
- Smith, Audrey D., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 42)
- Smith, Deborah J., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 43)
- Smith, Donnal V., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 44)
- Smith, Dwight C., Jr., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 45)
- Smith, Dwight C., Jr., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 46)
- Smith, Hugh MacKienze, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 47)
- Smith, Jack H., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 48)
- Smith, Paul, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 49)
- Smith, Ted Jay, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 50)
- Smith, Thomas Herbert, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 51)
- Smith, Tom, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 52)
- Smoot, James S., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 53)
- Sneed, Joseph, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 54)
- Snow, Dean R., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 55)
- Snow, Dean, 1995 (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 56)
- Snow, Frank, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 57)
- Snyder, Gerald, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 58)
- Snyder, Gerald W., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 59)
- Snyder, Patricia, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 60)
- Sogliuzzo, A. Richard, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 61)
- Solomon, Gary S., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 62)
- Solomon, Ruth, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 63)
- Solnick, Bruce B., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 64)
- Sorenson, Gail P., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 65)
- Sorenson, Gail, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 66)
- Soule, Marion, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 67)
- Spalek, John M., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 68)
- Spatz Widom, Cathy, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 69)
- Spauster, Edward, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 70)
- Speckhard, Roy A., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 71)
- Speckhard, Roy, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 72)
- Spellman, Seth W., 1967-1985 (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 73)
- Spellman, Seth W., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 74)
- Spenard, Raymond J., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 75)
- Spencer, Linda Lisa, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 76)
- Spielmann, Gary, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 77)
- Spitzer, Dean R., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 78)
- Spizman, Lawrence M., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 79)
- Squatriglia, Robert W., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 80)
- Squires, Donald, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 81)
- Sroka, Suzanne Gaidier, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 82)
- Stallman, Esther, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 83)
- Standing, Theodore G., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 84)
- Stanfill, Nancy, 1996 (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 85)
- Starr, David, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 86)
- Stauffer, Donald, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 87)
- Stanisky, Leonard, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 88)
- Steen, Ivan D., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 89)
- Steger, Barbara M., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 90)
- Steger, Joseph A., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 91)
- Steinberg, Ronnie, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 92)
- Steinberg, Ronnie, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 93)
- Stelzer, Leigh, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 94)
- Stern, Helman I., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 95)
- Stern, Susan, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 96)
- Stevens, Jane E., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 97)
- Stevens, Kathryn (Jerum), Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 98)
- Stevens, Laurel Sloat, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 99)
- Stevenson, Gordon, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 100)
- Stevenson, Sara H., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 101)
- Stever, Gertrude, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 102)
- Stewart, Bruce, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 103)
- Stewart, Bruce, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 104)
- Stewart, Jason, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 105)
- Stewart, Jason, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 106)
- Stewart, Jimmie, Jason, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 107)
- Stewart, Margaret M., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 108)
- Stewart, Margaret McBride, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 109)
- Stewart, Mary Ellen, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 110)
- Stewart, Ronald, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 111)
- Stewart, Thomas R., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 112)
- Stewart, William C., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 113)
- Stewart, William, Jr., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 114)
- Stienstra, Arthur L., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 115)
- Stierer, Robert A., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 116)
- Stierer, Robert A., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 117)
- Stigliani, William M., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 118)
- Stock, Elizabeth, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 119)
- Stockin, Bruce C., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 120)
- Stoessinger, John G., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 121)
- Stokes, Dean Ellen C., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 122)
- Stone, David E., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 123)
- Stone, Lois, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 124)
- Articles "Stoneman, Kate" bibliography, Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 125)
- Stong, C.L., Undated (Box 37 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 126)
- Story, Harold S., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 1)
- Stout, Ronald M., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 2)
- Stout, Ronald M., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 3)
- Stout, Ronald M., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 4)
- Stratton, Howard H., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 5)
- Streun, Eleanor D., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 6)
- Stross, Raymond G., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 7)
- Stutz, John, Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 8)
- Suarez, Irma, Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 9)
- Suchon, Kathleen, Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 10)
- Sugarman, Robert, Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 11)
- Sullivan, Richard W., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 12)
- Suls, Jerry M., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 13)
- Sun, Chih-Ree, Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 14)
- Sun, Helen, Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 15)
- Sutton, George H., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 16)
- Suzuki, Kunihiro, Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 17)
- Svare, Bruce B., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 18)
- Swan, L. Alex, Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 19)
- Swanstrom, Todd, Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 20)
- Sweet, Jeffrey, Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 21)
- Sweetser, Albert G., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 22)
- Sweetser, Albert G., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 23)
- Sweetser, Albert G., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 24)
- Sweetser, Albert G., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 25)
- Sweetser, Albert G., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 26)
- Sweetser, Albert G., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 27)
- Sweetser, Albert G., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 28)
- Sweetser, Albert G., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 29)
- Swider, Andrew L., Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 30)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, 1990 (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 31)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, 1990 (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 32)
- Swygert, H. Patrick Inauguration Ceremony, 1991 April 5 (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 33)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 34)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 35)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, Undated (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 36)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, 1990-1995 (Box 38 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 37)
- Swygert, H. Patrick Photos, Undated (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 1)
- Swygert, H. Patrick Photos, Undated (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 2)
- Swygert, H. Patrick - Temple University background, 1990 (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 3)
- Swygert, H. Patrick Inauguration, 1991 April 5 (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 4)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, 1991 (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 5)
- Swygert, H. Patrick Biographical Sketch, 1992 (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 6)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, 1992 (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 7)
- Swygert, H.P. Biographical Sketch, 1993 March (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 8)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, 1993 (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 9)
- Swygert, H. Patrick NYS Special Commission on Educational Structure, Policies and Practices v.II, 1993 (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 10)
- Swygert, H. Patrick New York State Special Commission on Educational Structures, Policies and Practices v.I Report, 1993 (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 11)
- Swygert, H. Patrick Vita, 1993 August (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 12)
- Swygert, H. Patrick New York State Special Commission on Educational Structures, Policies and Practices v.III Report, 1993 (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 13)
- Swygert, H. Patrick Biographical Sketch, 1993 June-1993 August (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 14)
- Swygert, H. Patrick New York State Special Commission on Educational Structure, Policies and Practices V.III Report, 1993 (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 15)
- Swygert, H. Patrick Moreland Act Commission, 1993-1994 (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 16)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, 1994 (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 17)
- Swygert, H. Patrick - Post U. at A. (see also Howard University Folder), 1995 (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 18)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, 1995 (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 19)
- Swygert, H. Patrick - Howard University, 1995-1996 (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 20)
- Swygert, H. Patrick NYS State Special Commission on Educational Structure, Policies and Practices V.IV, Undated (Box 39 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 21)